So if you didn't see my last
video, I just got my wedding
ring today and I was a little
bit disappointed. Let me give
you a little bit of a backstory
before I do the whole reveal.
So the first design that I
created for this ring looked
like this. I wanted to do a band
with pavé crystals all around it
that go from green, brown, and
then like champagne and any
colors in between because my
eyes are green and my fiancé's
eyes are brown. So I So I
thought it was just a really
cute way to like represent us
and show us coming together.
Here's a picture of a ring that
I use as inspiration for the
actual color scheme of my
wedding ring. So now for the
ring reveal. I'm not upset that
it's like an ugly ring or
something. It's still gorgeous.
It's just not the colors that I
expected or hoped. So this is
the ring. I just don't really
see much green in it, which is
why I was a bit upset. It is
beautiful, it's just not what I
expected. So what do you guys
think? Am I crazy, or should I
say something?